Okay now that I have combed protein based conditioner throughout her hair I need to wrap it in plastic.
The reason I'm going to put plastic on her hair, or a plastic cap, either one will work.
But in case you don't have the plastic cap, the plastic saran wrap works just as good.
We want to totally wrap her hair in this.
Just make believe she's a leftover.
The plastic wrap sticks to itself.
She's totally wrapped.
You want to close it in.
And that's going to hold in the heat from her head.
The heat process helps the conditioner penetrate into the hair shaft to ensure proper coverage.
And it will not work without the plastic.
It doesn't work the same.
So you really need to, this holds your body heat in.
If you have availability to a dryer that's even better but you definitely want to put this plastic on here.
If you have a plastic cap that works good, too.
So either way.
Plastic cap or saran wrap.
And you can actually see it starting to heat up inside.
You can see the steam building up.
So that means we've got her wrapped properly.
And that's how you want to put the plastic on her scalp.
Make sure she's covered completely.